[
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [26, 25, 23, 23, 21, 24, 23, 22]?",
      "correctAnswer": "23",
      "options": [
        "22",
        "23",
        "24",
        "25"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [25, 25, 25, 25, 26, 22, 23, 24, 27]?",
      "correctAnswer": "25",
      "options": [
        "24",
        "25",
        "26",
        "27"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [23, 23, 23, 27, 28, 23, 23, 25, 24, 26]?",
      "correctAnswer": "23",
      "options": [
        "22",
        "23",
        "24",
        "25"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [28, 29, 24, 29, 29, 26, 27, 25]?",
      "correctAnswer": "29",
      "options": [
        "28",
        "29",
        "30",
        "31"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [27, 30, 30, 26, 30, 28, 30, 25, 29]?",
      "correctAnswer": "30",
      "options": [
        "29",
        "30",
        "31",
        "32"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [31, 27, 30, 28, 27, 29, 27, 26, 27, 27]?",
      "correctAnswer": "27",
      "options": [
        "26",
        "27",
        "28",
        "29"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [30, 29, 31, 28, 30, 30, 32, 27]?",
      "correctAnswer": "30",
      "options": [
        "29",
        "30",
        "31",
        "32"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [30, 29, 32, 33, 29, 28, 31, 29, 29]?",
      "correctAnswer": "29",
      "options": [
        "28",
        "29",
        "30",
        "31"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [32, 31, 29, 31, 34, 31, 30, 33, 31, 31]?",
      "correctAnswer": "31",
      "options": [
        "30",
        "31",
        "32",
        "33"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [32, 33, 34, 31, 32, 32, 30, 35]?",
      "correctAnswer": "32",
      "options": [
        "31",
        "32",
        "33",
        "34"
      ]
    }
]